theawareshow.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - The Aware Show

The personal information collected from this web site may be used for a variety of purposes including identification, registration, authentication, on-line transactions, and marketing. The personal data of customers and web site visitors may be stored indefinitely and may be collected and processed in one or more data bases maintained directly or indirectly by The Website Owner, operator, or their agents. By providing personal information to The Website Owner, operator, or their agents, you agree and understand that The Website Owner, operator, or their agents may access, store and use this information for a variety of purposes including identification, registration, authentication, on-line transactions, and marketing (unless you have opted out of receiving marketing solicitations) in any of the countries in which The Website Owner, operator, or their agents maintain offices, including the United States.

Personal Information

You should be aware that The Website Owner, operator, or their agents will disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal process; (2) respond to any claims; or (3) protect the rights, property or personal safety of The Website Owner, operator, or their agents, our customers or the public.

Cookies – What They Are and Why They Are Used

Like many companies that provide web sites, The Website Owner, operator, or their agents may use “cookies” in order to better understand and serve the needs of our on-line visitors. A cookie is a small text file that a web page server places on your hard drive. Cookies function as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies are used to let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. This helps us to be more efficient in serving you because it permits us to determine what information and web pages you may be especially interested in viewing. Cookies also can be used to determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. If you do not wish to have a cookie set when you visit our web pages, you may alter the settings in your browser to prevent them. The browser can be “instructed” to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. However, by not accepting cookies, some web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.

Personal Information Related to Children

The Website Owner, operator, or their agents does not intend to collect personal information from children who identify themselves as being under 18 years of age. Children should not provide personal information on this web site, and should ask their parents to submit a request on their behalf if they want to receive information related to this site. The Website Owner, operator, or their agents encourages parents to take an active interest in their children’s use of the Internet. The Website Owner, operator, or their agents Respects and Protects Your Personal Information and will take reasonable measures to protect the information you share with us. Whenever you give us sensitive information (such as when you register with a personal identity and password) The Website Owner, operator, or their agents will take commercially reasonable steps to establish a secure connection with your web browser.

“Opting Out”

If you choose to “opt out” of receiving information from The Website Owner, operator, or their agents, its partners or other companies or organizations at the time you submit personal information, or you would like to stop receiving information from The Website Owner, operator, or their agents, you may notify us at any time by sending us an e-mail message or a written notification to the email or postal address indicated in the next paragraph. Please include your name, address (including country), and/or e-mail address when you contact us. If you notify us that you wish to “opt out” after you initially provided us with personal information, we will no longer share your personal information with other companies and organizations subsequent to your “opt out” notification. However, any information we provided to other companies or organizations prior to receiving your “opt-out” request will not be recalled.

Updating, Reviewing, and Deleting Your Information

You can help The Website Owner, operator, or their agents to maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any change to your address, phone number, e-mail address or other information by sending us an e-mail message to the email address listed on the ‘About/Contact Us’ page or by notifying us in writing at the address listed on the ‘About/Contact Us’ page of this website.

Links to Other Sites

The Website Owner, operator, or their agents are not responsible for the privacy practices of other Website Owners, operators, or their agents sites to which The Website Owner, operator, or their agents web site(s) may link. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of these sites before you provide them with personal information.

Questions or Concerns

The Website Owner, operator, or their agents welcomes your questions and comments regarding this policy. If you believe that The Website Owner, operator, or their agents has not adhered to this policy please notify us with a message sent to the email address listed on the ‘About/Contact Us’ page or in writing at the address listed on the ‘About/Contact Us’ page of this website, attn: Customer Service/Privacy and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to identify and remedy the problem.

Changes to this Policy

We may from time to time update this policy. When we do so, we will post notice of any revisions on this site. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you visit our web site.
